Help on function urlretrieve in module urllib.request:

urlretrieve(url, filename=None, reporthook=None, data=None)
    Retrieve a URL into a temporary location on disk.
    
    Requires a URL argument. If a filename is passed, it is used as
    the temporary file location. The reporthook argument should be
    a callable that accepts a block number, a read size, and the
    total file size of the URL target. The data argument should be
    valid URL encoded data.
    
    If a filename is passed and the URL points to a local resource,
    the result is a copy from local file to new file.
    
    Returns a tuple containing the path to the newly created
    data file as well as the resulting HTTPMessage object.

